

ARMAN GOLCHOUBIAN

UI/UX Designer

(+98)935 933 7840

arman.golchoubian@yahoo.com

Profile

I'm a Graphic & UI/UX Designer with a strong background and experience in different areas including UI/UX design, motion graphics & Visual design.

Designer focused on building brands and creating digital experiences.

Fascinated by technology, branding, and innovation and the impact that design has on each one.

★ Skills

Design

Research

Persona/Storyboard

User storie/ User journey/ User Flow

Wireframe

Prototype

Web Responsive Design

Storyboarding

Interaction Design

Visual Design

Web Design

iOS, Android Design

A/B Testing

Usability Test

Contextual Research

Agile/Scrum and Jira & Confluence

HTML / CSS

Software

Figma

Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere

Cinema 4D

Jira Software

Language

Persian English

Education 2006 - 2008

Emam Sadegh University

Associate's degree Computer Software

Experience

Mazinoor Factory Graphic & UI/UX Designer

May 2019 - Up to the present

Leading luminaire manufacturer in the Iran, with over 40 years of experience. There is a great need to for design in Mazinoor various platforms as it deals with a wide range of individuals including customers, agents, architects and retailers.

- I always try to help the brand and it's sub-brands by doing research, A/B testing, Usability Test, web & application design and interaction design.
- Designing materials for online promotions for social media latforms, keeping brand guidelines in mind
- Designing user interfaces & user experiences, advertisement videos, motion graphics, catalogs, banners, posters, product packaging.

Mehraz Andishan Architecture

Sep 2017 - May 2018

Head of graphic design department

- Helped conceptualize, design and develop digital and social communications to be utilized across all channels
- Interacted with Creative Directors, Account Leads, Art Directors and Copywriters to develop creative concepts and assist in the execution of ideas through design
- · Led brainstorming sessions and design reviews
- Served as a key player in agency's evolving workflow process

Yalit Families Fitting

Nov 2016 - Sep 2017

UI/UX Designer

- Used diverse inputs to identify and define exciting new concepts, opportunities, and customer problems
- Developed creative concepts and implementations that are consistently on target with brand objectives
- Built solid understanding of the market and brand dynamics of assigned client projects

Freelance graphic design

Jun 2012 - May 2019

Graphic & UI/UX Designer - Motion Graphics

- Designed engaging content in support of product needs and marketing initiatives
- Created layered files and print and web production ready files
- Collaborated with cross-functional design, development, and business teams to ensure all aspects of user experience have been thought through and optimized